<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:20:10 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
      <title>MGV Project</title>
      <link>/posts/mgv_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 23:20:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mgv_project/</guid>
      <description>Analyzing Connector Protein from MGV Database The MGV database from the paper, Metagenomic compendium of 189,680 DNA viruses from the human gut microbiome contains 189,000 viral sequences sampled from the bacteriophages residing in the human gut. Many of these viruses were previously unknown and the goal of this project is to create a general structure of the connector protein by obtaining and modeling many connector proteins whose sequences are available in the database.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HackDavis Project</title>
      <link>/posts/hackdavis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 23:20:10 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hackdavis/</guid>
      <description>Our project for HackDavis 2023:
Trouble in Moo Town
This project was inspired by our desire to build a game that would encourage folks to go outside and appreciate our beautiful campus. We decided to integrate this idea with a tour-like game that would help incoming freshmen and transfers navigate our huge campus!
Made in collaboration with Sai Suresh, Jenna Noueihed, and Meghana Manepalli.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Books</title>
      <link>/posts/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2023 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/books/</guid>
      <description>My top ten books:
1. The Goldfinch
Every page of this hefty tome is a work of art. Reading this book was about as easy as watching a movie, absolutely seamless transition from the page to a visual in your mind. It&amp;rsquo;s beautiful to see a (very human, very flawed) character grow up, admist tragedies, build friendships, some fleeting and some life-changing, and eventually just navigate life. Which all sounds very cliche and overdone in the bildungsroman genre, but what I think the Goldfinch does best is that Theo, the protagonist, is never made out to be especially talented or</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>/posts/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Greeting! This is an introduction post. This post tests the followings:
Hero image is in the same directory as the post. This post should be at top of the sidebar. Post author should be the same as specified in author.yaml file. </description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
